etronics.com 2002-06-05

# Etronics.com - Discount camcorders, DVD players, home audio, digital and 35mm cameras, VCR's, televisions plus small appliances.

Etronics is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the Etronics Web Site. When you visit a Web site displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, you can expect to be notified of:

1-What personally identifiable information is collected from you. 

2-The organization collecting the information 

3-How the information is used 

4-With whom this information may be shared. 

5-What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of this information 

6-The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Supremevideo.net control 

7-How you can correct any inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Etronics.com through email at [webmaster@Etronics.com](mailto:webmaster@Etronics.com) or by snail mail to: 

Webmaster  
Etronics  
37 Essex Street  
New York, NY 10002 

If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry within five business days or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe ([http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.html](http://www.truste.org/users/watchdog.html)). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

Information we gather from you.

When you visit Etronics.com, we collect information about your visit. We collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, and we log the length of time of your visit and the number of times you visit and purchase from us. We use this information to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors, and we use it to personalize the information you see on our website. Even more so, the IP Address is used to help identify you, your wish list and you’re past purchases.  The IP address is not at all linked to any personal identifiable information. We keep this information for our internal use; in order to personalize the site. For example, in the future, we may recommend products or features you may like based on what you have liked in the past

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). We use a third party to authorize and verify all credit card transaction made through on etronics.com. The billing address and phone number is used for verification purposes only your email address is used for multiple purposes; verification, log in and email order confirmations. The Contact information from the order form may be used to send information about order status to our customers. All users have the option of opting out of any communication to etronics.com by sending an email to [Webmaster@etronics.com](mailto:Webmaster@etronics.com) or by calling our customer service department at 800-541-1490. Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). We use a third party to authorize and verify all credit card transaction made through on etronics.com. The billing address and phone number is used for verification purposes only your email address is used for multiple purposes; verification, log in and email order confirmations. The Contact information from the order form may be used to send information about order status to our customers. All users have the option of opting out of any communication to etronics.com by sending an email to [Webmaster@etronics.com](mailto:Webmaster@etronics.com) or by calling our customer service department at 800-541-1490. 

We also personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations For Electronics, Music, Games and other merchandise that might be of interest to you. 

When you create a Wish List, you must be a registered user, we ask for your and an email address. We use your name and personal description to identify your Wish List; we use your name and your email address to process and fulfill your Wish List orders. You can also choose to provide e-mail addresses of friends and family with whom you would like to share your list. We'll e-mail the recipients that you choose to tell them about your Wish List and its contents, and how they can easily access it. We will not disclose or send promotional e-mails to those recipient addresses provided only to the Wish List service. 

If a user elects to use our email a friend program for informing a friend about our site or products, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address.  Etronics will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site.  Etronics stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.  This email address is removed form our database once the email has is sent. 

When you sign up for our Newsletter, we need only an e-mail address--which is used to send the information requested. When submitting to the Newsletter mailing list, you will not receive separate emails from other marketers as a result. You might receive offers from our company including those made through the newsletter itself, which, of course, you have elected to receive. Customers requesting a newsletter may receive emails notifying them of Etronics special promotions and deals. If you choose to be removed from the newsletter please either click on the unsubscribe link from the actual newsletter or email [webmaster@etronics.com](mailto:webmaster@etronics.com).

Our site uses cookies to store information. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to remember your name and your customer id. This allows you to leave our site, come back later, and still view contents in your wish list and purchases made in the past. These cookies allow Etronics to better understand, in aggregate, the preferences of our users and thereby create new services that better attend to those preferences. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them.

Special Relationships  
  
We have an affiliate program through Commission Junction that allows other websites to earn money by directing people to our website. When you sign up as an affiliate, your contact information (website address and related information, email address, mailing and payment addresses, and contact information) is sent directly to us were we activate your affiliate status and pays you based on the sales you generate. We do not share any information with these affiliates other than the order total, which is needed for commission purposes. Commission Junctions  [privacy policy](http://www.cj.com/privacy.asp) can also be evaluated at www.cj.com

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of those linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. Etronics is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Security

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

Etronics has very strict policies and procedures designed to protect the privacy of our customers and subscribers. We will never share or sell your personal information with any external organization. Any personal information you wish to provide is also protected internally. All personnel with access to personal information are aware of our policies. Any breach of policy would result in immediate dismissal. Sometimes we use aggregated information to determine trends and visitor needs. Some aggregated information is analyzed and used as input to improve our site or is presented to clients as market research; however, no personal information is divulged.

If you decide to submit your email address to us in order to receive a price quote you may be assured that you will not receive separate emails from other marketers as a result. All inquiries are used for a one-time purpose only. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. Online via my account 
  2. You can send email to [Service@Etronics.com](mailto:Service@supremevideo.com)
  3. You can call the following telephone number: 1800-541-1490 
  4. You can send mail to the following postal address: 

Customer Service  
37 Essex Street  
New York, NY 10002 

## Correct/Update

We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the personal information that you have provided to us. During the online ordering process you can review, change, or delete the information that you have submitted. You may change any of your personal information in your my account online at any time. We encourage you to update your information when it changes. You may ask to have the information in your my account be deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past purchases, you cannot delete information associated with past purchases. 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. Online via my account 
  2. You can send email to [Service@Etronics.com](mailto:Service@supremevideo.com)
  3. You can call the following telephone number: 1800-541-1490 
  4. You can send mail to the following postal address: 

Customer Service  
37 Essex Street,  
New York, NY 10002 

We welcome your questions and comments. Please send e-mails to [webmaster@Etronics.com](mailto:webmaster@etronics.com).

Privacy Changes  
Whenever we change our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our homepage indicating that a new version is available. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Contacting the WebSite   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at: 

Webmaster Etronics  
37 Essex Street  
New York, NY 10002  
[webmaster@Etronics.](mailto:webmaster@Etronics.com)Com
